Iginari Expedition
With our rainbow child, Sternus.
Iinari and Grass-chan
I look forward to working with you
Karen Tachibana and
Mizuki Hikaru.
I'm Mizuki Hikaru.
I'm Karen and Hikaru.
I see you're Karen and Hikaru today.
What's going on?
Is this the expedition uniform?
Why are you always in jerseys? Is this the expedition uniform? They're always in jerseys.
What is it? What's wrong with this outfit?
I'm Patricia today.
I feel like I've been made to wear it.
I've been wearing this outfit from the start because it has something to do with today's expedition.
It's so delicious!
Well, I'd like to announce today's exploration, and today's exploration is to make and eat gelato.
Today we're going to explore Sendai Gelato and Gelaco, which opened in April at Eby's.
That's why I'm dressed like a patissier.
How do you like it?
I've eaten one of their pastries.
It was really delicious.
We all ordered different flavours.
We each got a bite of everything.
We shared it.
We ate it.
It was really good.
What about you, Karen?
It was delicious then, too.
And I got to eat it as a penguin.
In a disguise.
In disguise.
There's been a lot of talk on Instagram recently.
I've been hearing a lot about it.
I wanted to go back to eat there
I was there today.
I've heard a lot about you and
I'd like to make it and try it.
I'd like to try it, so let's move on to the restaurant.
Let's go.
Okay, we've arrived at the shop. We're going to try a few things now.
But before that, I'd like to talk to one of the staff.
I'm Lumika.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
Lumika-san.
Pleased to meet you.
My Lumika-san.
She's here.
Nice to meet you today.
Let's talk about a few things first, shall we?
Yes, ma'am.
How long have you been working here as Mr Geraco?
As Mr Geraco?
An impostor?
We opened in April.
It's only been about a month.
About a month.
What did you do originally?
Interviewing? Interviews?
Interviews?
I had various other jobs.
I'm putting it down now.
It's a bit different.
It's the year I turned 21.
Year 22.
Okay, the middle one.
Wait a minute.
It's okay, but be friendly.
I have to ask about the shop first.
Just in case. I know, but...
What kind of shop is it?
What kind of shop?
Just the way it is.
Yes, it's a place that serves great serrato.
What flavours go with it?
We have 12 flavours.
Twelve flavours.
Yes, we have 12 flavours.
The most popular will be Pikachu and cream cheese.
Mmm.
The pikachu was delicious.
Oh, really? I highly recommend the Pikachu.
I see.
About today...
I'd like to give you two some experience in the kitchen.
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
Can you do it?
I'm a complete amateur.
I think I can do it.
It sounds difficult.
It's difficult.
But if you try, you might be surprised.
Well, then...
I'll be asking you for tips and tricks.
I'm looking forward to working with you today.
Let's go inside.
What's up?
What happened?
Did something happen at Take 1?
Sounds like something happened.
I'm sorry to bother you, but we're going to have to go inside.
I'm still a bit fuzzy from here.
Let's have Master teach us both a little.
Master, a little practice, please.
Today you will make a double churat.
Double? Yes, Master.
You'll hold the double churat.
Cruise first.
Yes, sir.
Cruise.
We're going to build the foundation.
The foundation.
Build the foundation.
Like this.
Oh!
Foundation.
Power.
It's going to take a lot of strength.
Yes, it does.
It depends on the flavour.
Yes, some flavours need a lot of force.
Yes, they do.
I don't think so. We're both macho types.
I'll take care of it.
You say that a lot.
Like that, egg-shaped.
Eh, beautiful.
In the crevice.
Like that.
Oh! That's amazing! Beautiful! And that completes the double 2345.
Six.
Seven.
Fourteen.
1516, you're going to move it the first time, right, and we've practised, so let's just take this one step at a time.
It's called practice.
Okay, well...
Shall we start with Hikaru?
Let's try it.
How often do you say that?
If you weren't doing this job...
What would you like to do if you weren't doing this job? I'm asked...
"An ice-cream maker.
I'd like to be a good ice-cream maker.
I want to be a good ice-cream maker.
I see.
I'll do my best.
So this is where you'll find out if you're cut out for the job?
Yes, I do.
I don't know what I would have done if I'd gone that way.
But my manager, captain...
"You don't have the arm strength for it.
What the hell is he talking about?
So I'll do my best today.
Here we go.
Is it hard?
Hard.
You need strength.
Yes, sir.
This looks hard.
I got a lot.
Service.
Service is good.
Foundation. Master, what do you think of this?
Get it in order.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Good, good, good, good, jazz!
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm practicing.
Yeah, yeah.
You good? I'm good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Fat!
It's so fat!
You know, just now, the master was a bit more precise, like this.
Raise it up like this to clean it up.
Raise it up.
Like this, like this.
But you can still get it.
Usually, you have to go down like this.
You feel like you want to do it, don't you?
That's the hard part.
But for a first time...
You're really good.
That's enough practice for now.
Would you like to try it next time, Karen?
Please do.
By the way, how many months does it take for someone who has really joined to be able to do it?
It depends on how many times you join, but I think that after about five times, you start to get a feel for it.
But I start practising on the day I join. Then you aim for it. But that's the thing, isn't it? I get a bit nervous when I'm being watched by customers.
There are also people filming with cameras.
I see.
I'm very nervous.
I'm very nervous. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best to make the horn stand up.
Let's go, behind you.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll put a lot of effort into it.
I have a quantity standard book.
There is a lot down there.
I bought this one while I was doing it a lot.
This much.
very good at it
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh!
You're so beautiful!
Yay!
So beautiful here.
Did you see Hikaru's earlier?
Here, start here.
Go downstairs.
Oh, my God, what's happening? It's hollow in reverse.
It's like going into a surf wave.
It looks like a heart. It looks a bit like a heart.
That's cute. That's difficult.
What was I supposed to do?
I let it go at first.
I put that one in the catheter, and then I just put it right up there.
Like this?
Okay. - Okay.
Like this.
Now it's like this, like this.
Yes, that's right.
Then you can make it a little nicer.
I see.
It's difficult.
The senses.
Yes, it's difficult because the senses get used to it.
It doesn't turn out like this.
I see.
Well, I guess we're done practicing now.
Yes, we're ready to go live.
We don't have five days.
We'll need you to make the next one for the customers.
Make it for the customers who are coming now.
Okay.
I'll go live first, Hikaru-san.
The guests are coming, so let's wait.
Let's wait.
Ah...
Welcome.
Ah, a customer's here, isn't it, customer?
They're here.
How can I help you?
Yes, well, I have a triple cup.
Triple?
Triple? I've never done it up north before.
First time.
Yes, in Yurokande.
In a pub.
Yes, in the Yurokan.
What flavour do you want?
From Shiogama.
Milk for letters and
New for a limited time only
Strawberries from Yomogi Yamamoto Farm.
Strawberries from Yomogi Yamamoto Farm, new for three hours only.
Oh!
Yes...
Made with a strawberry base.
A strawberry base?
I like them.
Oh, really?
I've only worked here for 10 minutes.
Are you going to say "I'm going"?
I'm doing it now.
Don't you have to say it? Is that...
Did they say, "Are you ready yet? They haven't said anything yet.
Not yet. Before they say it.
I'm just gonna go ahead and nail her.
Okay, okay, okay.
How do you make a triple?
Smaller.
Maybe harder.
It's hard.
Go for it.
I'll be waiting for you, sir.
Why don't you say something?
I'm working on it.
He's so angry.
He's very angry.
Very angry.
You're in luck.
Why is it so easy to have kids?
Hang in there.
Just do your best.
What are you doing?
I'm working on it.
Let's go!
Oh!
I'll show you!
Oh, my God, that's great!
Why are you showing off?
To say, "I did it well!
Here we go.
Well done, let's eat.
Yum, yum, yum.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yum.
It's good.
That's great.
Here you go, sir.
Great, I'll take it.
This is EB's YouTube.
Can I ask you to come on?
No, it's fine.
Just a little taste.
Oh, my.
Mugwort.
Looks good.
It looks good!
Hmm?
Yum! Yomogi.
I love it.
Why is it good?
I've only been here ten minutes.
Hikaru Itsuki, who's only been here ten minutes, gave it to me.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Seeing our customers smile is the best.
It's worth it.
Good, good, good.
That's what we're doing.
That's why we do what we do.
Master, how did you like Hikaru's smile?
It was great.
The glue was great.
He says he's working on it.
That's reassuring.
That's true.
It's about relieving anxiety.
That was great.
Next, Karen, let's go to work.
Okay, Karen, you're up next.
I don't know if the audience will show up.
I don't know.
We might have to wait.
Oh!
Sounds like a line. Aah! Aah! Excuse me, welcome.
I'd like a triple, please.
Oh! Triple!
That sounds like a line.
How to theme
How to triple
What flavour do you want?
Do you have any recommendations?
Recommendations?
Yes, I do.
I'm here now.
We have a new menu.
Yamamoto Farm's strawberry vinegar and
Chocolate chip and
Mugwort.
The most popular items are cream cheese and pistachio.
Also, the most popular items are cream cheese and pistachio.
But they are all delicious.
Yum!
Then I'll have strawberries, cream cheese and chocolate chips from Yamato Farm, please.
We're making them now, please wait.
So far, so good.
What food do you like, by the way?
What food do you like?
I like jajar noodles.
You like jajar noodles?
Are you from Iwate?
I'm from Miyagi.
You're from Miyagi?
I see.
Do you make them while talking like this?
Like this.
What do you like? I like o-hagi and pumpkin salad.
I also like mugwort, so the menu is very familiar.
Mugwort? Chocolate chips and cream cheese.
And these little noodles.
How long have I been here?
That's amazing.
Six months, a year.
Actually, just now.
It's our first customer.
I'll put all my heart into it.
Are you waiting?
I'll wait for you. Yes! Yes! Delicious!
Maid cafe?
Thank you for waiting! Please eat as much as you can!
Thank you very much!
Please come again!
Yes! Thank you!
Whoo-hoo!
It's done! Great!
How was it, Master? He's just now.
It's difficult to talk to him.
It's difficult.
I was wondering if you worked here, if it's all right to talk like that. Is it okay to talk like that? It's difficult to talk while we're having a conversation, so it's difficult.
I was wondering if you worked there.
Is it okay to talk like that?
What's your favourite food? Or...
Yes.
I've never cooked other food in a telework shop before.
How long do I look like I've been working? And...
You don't normally ask that in any profession.
I used to ask about my destiny.
Like at a party.
How old do I look? Like that.
Yes, I guess that's a good question in customer service - it was to get a rise out of me. Like at a party. How old do I look? Like that.
- I guess that's good customer service. It was good.
- It makes Shark feel good. Oh, I'm so glad.
- So, since we're here, let's have a taste, or rather, a tasting.
- Let's have some of the gelato you made yourself.
What flavour is it?
This is chocolate chip.
Let's try the chocolate chip.
Bon appétit!
Eat it with me.
I can't resist.
It's so cute.
What's that?
Delicious.
And you, Karen?
I'll start with the walnuts.
Bon appétit.
Yummy.
Yummy?
But with a gentle taste.
You could eat a whole lot of it.
Like the taste of the ingredients.
It has a gentle taste.
Strawberry milk.
Oh, it's delicious.
Strawberry milk is delicious! Delicious! Strawberry milk is delicious.
It's kind of sweet.
Tastes like a pretty girl.
Wow.
Are you okay? That.
Can an old man like me eat it?
Tastes like a pretty girl.
It's okay. I think I'll just...
I think I'm gonna make a face like this.
What kind of face?
What's that, Miss Cullen?
Mugwort.
It smells amazing.
It's so much mugwort.
Wow, I love it.
You like it?
Yeah, I like it a lot.
See three?
Yeah. - Yeah.
What are they? Hikaru's three.
Peace Knights.
Peace statio.
I once got one from a Wasagi who was eating them.
They were so good, I decided to try them again.
They're popular, you know, because...
This one, this one, this one.
There's no doubt about it.
The aroma is so rich.
I can see why it's number one.
I see why cream cheese is number one, too.
I see. Cream cheese, yes.
It's definitely dense and rich.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Booby.
Sometimes it's still a little bit bland, so it tastes different where you eat it.
I see.
It seems to go well with the others.
Triple, Hikaru Special and Karen Special made today.
I wish you'd do the same.
Who saw this?
This combination.
I'd like you to put the stomachs together.
Stomach plate.
I want you to do the same thing with the stomach. I've been eating dog ice cream, and I'm still slipping on dog ice cream.
I'm really happy that there are so many different flavours, and...
I'm going to go through all of them and I'm going to get a fresh one.
It's really good.
How did you like it, Karen?
It was really good the last time I had it.
I'd like to recommend it to everyone.
So I thought it would be great if you could teach us how to make it like this and tell everyone about it on the video.
I think I was able to convey the charm of the restaurant to everyone through the video.
I really want everyone to try it and conquer them all!
It's really delicious and I wholeheartedly recommend it!
Thank you very much for a fun and wonderful experience!
Thank you very much.
And what a surprise!
I've just been informed that there's a special offer.
Can you explain what the benefit is?
Yes. Let's say you order a single from Gelaco.
And you get a double for the same price!
Here it comes! Yes, yes!
One size up service!
That's right!
So here comes the double!
What's with the "coming"?
They're offering a one-size-fits-all service.
That's why it's limited to 100 people.
The first 100 people to tell us they saw this video
If you tell us when you order.
You'll get that score.
If I order a triple...
I get a single?
No, you can't have four.
No, there's no such thing as four on the menu.
I'm going back.
Oh, no. It's a trap!
It's a trap!
Don't try to end up lying. At least correct us.
I'd like you to come to Gerako as a result of this video.
Definitely come!
So today we visited Zero Up shop Gelaco in Sendai!
We hope you all enjoy the same menu and all the different kinds of food that we have on offer!
Well, thank you very much for all the smiles you've given to the people involved in today's event!
Thank you very much.